<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Valhalla</title>
  <subtitle>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</subtitle>
  <link href="http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080/"/>
  <updated>2022-05-18T22:16:21.000+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//</id>
  <author>
    <name>Odin</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Pain Itself</title>
    <link href="http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//pain-itself/"/>
    <updated>2022-05-18T22:16:21.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//pain-itself/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Son, a woman is like a beer. They smell good, they look good, you&#39;d step over your own mother just to get one! But you can&#39;t stop at one. You wanna drink another woman!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;…And the fluffy kitten played with that ball of string all through the night. On a lighter note, a Kwik-E-Mart clerk was brutally murdered last night. Get ready, skanks! It&#39;s time for the truth train!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ll keep it short and sweet — Family. Religion. Friendship. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;These are the three demons you must slay if you wish to succeed in business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;That&#39;s why I love elementary school, Edna.&lt;/em&gt; The children believe anything you tell them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-good-is-money-if-it-cant-inspire-terror-in-your-fellow-man&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What good is money if it can&#39;t inspire terror in your fellow man?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids, we need to talk for a moment about Krusty Brand Chew Goo Gum Like Substance. We all knew it contained spider eggs, but the hantavirus? That came out of left field. So if you&#39;re experiencing numbness and/or comas, send five dollars to antidote, PO box… Please do not offer my god a peanut.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Coming soon</title>
    <link href="http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//coming-soon/"/>
    <updated>2022-05-18T16:41:38.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//coming-soon/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is Valhalla, a brand new site by Odin that&#39;s just getting started. Things will be up and running here shortly, but you can &lt;a href=&quot;http://11ty-ghost.wtf:8080//feed.xml#/portal/&quot;&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; in the meantime if you&#39;d like to stay up to date and receive emails when new content is published!&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
